<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
      <string name="app_name">Car Bluetooth FM</string>
      <string name="app_name_show">Car Bluetooth Player</string>
      <string name="app_version">Software version: %1$s</string>
      <string name="btn_change">Change frequency</string>
      <string name="btn_bt">Bluetooth Settings</string>
      <string name="btn_ok">OK</string>
      <string name="btn_cannel">Cancel</string>
      <string name="btn_allow">Allow</string>
      <string name="btn_refused">Refuse</string>
      <string name="btn_open">Enabled</string>
      <string name="btn_close">Disabled</string>
      <string name="btn_next">Next</string>
      <string name="btn_exit">Exit</string>
      <string name="delete">Delete</string>
      <string name="delete_success">Deleted successfully</string>
      <string name="delete_fail">Delete failed</string>
      <string name="default_music_app">Default music player:</string>
      <string name="fm_but">FM transmitter</string>
      <string name="fm_bt_note">Not connected</string>
      <string name="fm_bt_lost">BT connection lost</string>
      <string name="fm_title">FM</string>
      <string name="fm_mhz">MHz</string>
      <string name="fm_note">Please adjust car\'s radio frequency</string>
      <string name="fm_set_note">Frequency set!</string>
      <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
      <string name="No_Link_FM">Please plug in your RoidMi</string>
      <string name="No_Data">No data</string>
      <string name="No_Create_File">Cannot create file</string>
      <string name="Net_not_connected">Please check if network is available.</string>
      <string name="space_insufficient">Insufficient space</string>
      <string name="No_WIFI">You are using mobile data plan! Charges may apply. To continue, press OK.</string>
      <string name="about">About</string>
      <string name="auto_title">Start mode</string>
      <string name="auto_info">Music player mode</string>
      <string name="auto_info_title">Please select startup mode</string>
      <string name="auto_state_default">Default</string>
      <string name="auto_state_click">Click</string>
      <string name="auto_state_play">Play</string>
      <string name="auto_state_click_info">Press OK to open default player</string>
      <string name="auto_state_play_info">Launches player and starts music</string>
      <string name="auto_bt_disconnected">Do it after BT connects successfully</string>
      <string name="auto_prompt_default">Default.</string>
      <string name="auto_prompt_click">Long press open.</string>
      <string name="auto_prompt_play">Auto play. Restart bluetooth to take effect.</string>
      <string name="bt_not_open">Bluetooth is not open</string>
      <string name="bt_link_title">Bluetooth:</string>
      <string name="bt_link_ok_info">Bluetooth connection is okay</string>
      <string name="bt_link_ok">Bound</string>
      <string name="bt_link_fail">Unbound</string>
      <string name="channel_change">FM</string>
      <string name="channel_set_title">Set frequency</string>
      <string name="channel_send_title">FM transmission frequency: %1$sMHZ</string>
      <string name="channel_send_current">Current frequency</string>
      <string name="channel_prompt">Synchronize car frequency</string>
      <string name="channel_recommend">Recommended frequency</string>
      <string name="download_fail_nofilename">File error (400) </string>
      <string name="drive_title_today">Today with recording</string>
      <string name="drive_title">Driving record</string>
      <string name="drive_title_drive">with</string>
      <string name="drive_title_drive_today">Today Driving:</string>
      <string name="drive_title_hour">h</string>
      <string name="drive_title_minute">stars</string>
      <string name="drive_near_info">%1$s lane%2$s</string>
      <string name="drive_time_0">"Core rice, surprises. 
      The rush to enjoy the fun of it belongs to you"</string>
      <string name="drive_time_30_1">"Congratulations, green lane road has been to achieve the ultimate
      We will leave you on China's green travel history"</string>
      <string name="drive_time_30_2">"Congratulations, you have a green lane of people
      You have the top in China driving green chart"</string>
      <string name="drive_time_30_3">"You have to love more and more environmentally friendly
      A little bit of effort every day, our goal even closer"</string>
      <string name="drive_time_60">"Oh well, let us realize together
      Driving does not exceed one hour per day dream it"</string>
      <string name="drive_time_120">Congratulations, green travel on the road took another step forward</string>
      <string name="drive_time_300_1">"Congratulations, smart driving Tyrant standings leaving your footprints
      Then use a little more every day, you will experience more fun oh"</string>
      <string name="drive_time_300_2">"wow, driving more than two hours per day
      Rui meters Tyrant list will have your place"</string>
      <string name="drive_time_300_more_1">"wow, you are a Chinese driving a Tyrant</string>
      <string name="drive_time_300_more_2">"wow, you have the top ranked Chinese Tyrant
      The mood is not very far ahead it was great!"</string>
      <string name="firmware">Firmware</string>
      <string name="firmware_name">Car Bluetooth FM</string>
      <string name="firmware_version">Firmware Version</string>
      <string name="firmware_update">Firmware Update</string>
      <string name="feed_back">Feedback</string>
      <string name="defout_contact">Your contact information (email, phone, QQ)</string>
      <string name="defout_content">Thanks for your feedback, we will carefully listen to your suggestions and comments.</string>
      <string name="fb_contact_empty">Information can not be empty!</string>
      <string name="fb_contact_error">Information malformed!</string>
      <string name="fb_content_empty">Feedback can not be empty!</string>
      <string name="fb_send">Send</string>
      <string name="fb_sending">Sending ...</string>
      <string name="fb_send_success">Sent successfully</string>
      <string name="fb_send_fail">Failed to send</string>
      <string name="feed_back_list_null1">We are looking forward to hear from you,</string>
      <string name="feed_back_list_null2">to bring you the best experience!</string>
      <string name="guide">boot</string>
      <string name="guide_use">Reconfigure</string>
      <string name="guide_title">Car Bluetooth FM</string>
      <string name="guide_login">Login</string>
      <string name="guide_1">Log, you agree to abide by Millet</string>
      <string name="guide_2">and</string>
      <string name="guide_protocol"> <u>User Agreement</u></string>
      <string name="guide_privacy_policyl"><u>Privacy Policy</u></string>
      <string name="guide_start_up">boot from the start</string>
      <string name="guide_start_up_info1">ensure the normal operation of the program</string>
      <string name="guide_start_up_info2">After the setup is successful, press the Back key to return the phone in this screen</string>
      <string name="guide_start_up_setting">Open from startup settings</string>
      <string name="guide_install">Dongle installation</string>
      <string name="guide_install_info">Plug the dongle into the cigarette lighter</string>
      <string name="guide_install_ok">Ok, dongle plugged!</string>
      <string name="guide_bt">Bluetooth connectivity</string>
      <string name="guide_bt_info">Please go to the Bletooth system settings to pair your phone with the dongle</string>
      <string name="guide_bt_link_info">After successful Bluetooth pairing, press the return key return here.</string>
      <string name="guide_bt_setting">Go to BT settings</string>
      <string name="guide_bt_success">Bluetooth connection is successful</string>
      <string name="guide_bt_success_info">Your phone is successfully connected to the dongle</string>
      <string name="voice_detection_title">Voice Detection</string>
      <string name="voice_detection_tip">Click to send a sound to detect whether the connection is successful</string>
      <string name="send_voice">Send sound</string>
      <string name="send_voice_fail">Did not hear the sound, change the frequency FM and return</string>
      <string name="send_voice_success">I heard the sound, go to the next step</string>
      <string name="next">Next</string>
      <string name="defalut_player">The default music player</string>
      <string name="defalut_player_detail">You can change the default player in the settings later</string>
      <string name="begin_use">Let\'s go!</string>
      <string name="fm_setting">Frequency settings</string>
      <string name="fm_setting_detial">The car FM frequency for @ should be set at:</string>
      <string name="fm_setting_info">Set the recommended frequency on your radio.</string>
      <string name="go_to">Next</string>
      <string name="help">Help</string>
      <string name="help_other">Common Problems</string>
      <string name="help_title">Help</string>
      <string name="help_Q1">1, Bluetooth cell phone search is not"Rui meters Bluetooth Player"</string>
      <string name="help_A1">Operation Tip: first player hardware from the cigarette lighter hole unplugged then re-insert the cigarette lighter hole, Bluetooth phone reopen closed interval 10S, click on search for new devices.</string>
      <string name="help_Q2">2, the player Bluetooth connection is not</string>
      <string name="help_A2">Operation Tip: After you reinsert the player off the cigarette lighter hole, click on search for new devices, then reconnect the player.</string>
      <string name="help_Q3">3, the Bluetooth connection is successful, no car audio sound</string>
      <string name="help_A3">Operation Tip: Go to APP, click on the [Home] FM transmit frequency, transmit frequency set about the player, click on the FM transmitter FM after seeing the success of the message, the car FM FM modulation set by frequency.</string>
      <string name="help_Q4">4, the music player is not used in their player</string>
      <string name="help_A4">Operation Tip: Go to APP, click on the default start page of [], select their common player can.</string>
      <string name="help_Q5">5, after setting the Auto Play mode, you can not automatically open the music player</string>
      <string name="help_A5">Operation Tip: the phone system settings in Car Bluetooth FM applications to back-office applications protected. Reference: enter the mobile phone [Setup], click [back] protected application, click Bluetooth FM applications behind the switch.</string>
      <string name="help_Q6">6, after switching mode setting has no effect</string>
      <string name="help_A6">Operation Tip: After the mode switch, the connection start to take effect from the next Bluetooth, Bluetooth to reconnect.</string>
      <string name="help_Q7">7, do not like the Auto Play mode</string>
      <string name="help_A7">Operation Tip: Go to APP, click on the default start page of [], the [car] is set to [Auto Play] to close.</string>
      <string name="help_Q8">8, the voice prompts do not need</string>
      <string name="help_A8">Operation Tip: Go to APP, click on the icon for more APP upper right corner of the voice prompt [] [Close] to set.</string>
      <string name="help_Q9">9, how to switch the player's light color?</string>
      <string name="help_A9">Operation Tip: Click the More icon APP upper right corner, click the [light color], you can select the corresponding color.</string>
      <string name="help_Q10">10, the player can not be commonly used in auto-play mode?</string>
      <string name="help_A10">Operation Tip: Make sure that the player whether or not the update operation, if the updated software, please guide the player page click shut off.</string>
      <string name="help_Q11">11, part of the music class software can not use?</string>
      <string name="help_A11">Operation Tip: The software does not belong to the software within our hardware products control protocol, it is recommended to use the system player, cool dog music, everyday sounds, cool music and QQ music software</string>
      <string name="help_CC_Q1">whether the player is in the vicinity of the phone?</string>
      <string name="help_CC_A1">the player is connected via Bluetooth with the phone, the closer the players and mobile phones, the more beneficial to the player and a phone connection.</string>
      <string name="help_CC_Q2">Players Are there power?</string>
      <string name="help_CC_A2">If the players and cell phones are close together or not find, please check the power supply situation of the player, the player light blink, the player can pull out to re-inserted into the cigarette lighter.</string>
      <string name="help_CC_Q3">try to restart the Bluetooth?</string>
      <string name="help_CC_A3">If the player is in good supply, the phone still can not find, you can try the phone's Bluetooth turned off after re-open and re-search after a wait a bit player.</string>
      <string name="help_CC_Q4">and other players have cellphone?</string>
      <string name="help_CC_A4">If your player has, and other cellphone, and the binding of the phone are still near the player, then you need to turn off the phone's Bluetooth is already bound, and then re-use the new phone player search device.</string>
      <string name="help_CC_Q5">try to reconnect the phone?</string>
      <string name="help_CC_A5">Try to restart the phone, Bluetooth FM reopen the application.</string>
      <string name="help_CC_Q6">player is bad?</string>
      <string name="help_CC_A6">Pay attention to whether there are soot filled smoke residue, if any, please clean before inserting products</string>
      <string name="help_CC_Q7">who can not manually adjust the frequency of car FM how to do?</string>
      <string name="help_CC_A7">will adjust to a car FM frequency, and then transferred to the frequency corresponding to the frequency of app, click OK to</string>
      <string name="help_CC_Q8">why it is recommended to use an empty FM frequency adjusted?</string>
      <string name="help_CC_A8">FM signals will interfere with each other when the FM signal is too strong, you may not hear the product emit FM signal, causing a problem with FM transmitter, so cover according to the strength of the local frequencies, we recommend three for you empty frequency</string>
      <string name="help_CC_Q9">how best tuned to a frequency?</string>
      <string name="help_CC_A9">recommended frequencies may not necessarily be the best option in your city, you can try to manually increase or decrease in 0.1MHz FM to adjust the car without a radio frequency interference, but also remember to adjust to the same phone APP frequency. If for some down time to listen very OK, you are welcome to the city and the frequency of the"on"in the"feedback"to share with us, we can optimize frequency to recommend little friends in your city when the software iteration.</string>
      <string name="info_center">Info Center</string>
      <string name="login">Login</string>
      <string name="login_fail">Login failed</string>
      <string name="login_out">Logout account</string>
      <string name="login_out_info">Are you sure you want to log out?</string>
      <string name="LED">LED Colour</string>
      <string name="LED_title">Colour Settings</string>
      <string name="LED_prompt">Please choose LED colour</string>
      <string name="LED_toast">LED colour is set to %1$s</string>
      <string name="LED_red">Red</string>
      <string name="LED_green">Green</string>
      <string name="LED_blue">Blue</string>
      <string name="LED_orange">Orange</string>
      <string name="LED_qing">Cyan</string>
      <string name="LED_close">LED off</string>
      <string name="MI_Key_proofread">Pairing button</string>
      <string name="MI_Key_swap">This action will switch up and down keys to control the direction of</string>
      <string name="music">Default player</string>
      <string name="music_title">Music player</string>
      <string name="music_not_install">App is not installed</string>
      <string name="music_main_title">Selected Player:</string>
      <string name="music_main_default_title">Set default app!</string>
      <string name="music_mode">Autoplay</string>
      <string name="music_chose_app">Select application</string>
      <string name="music_info">m key to directly operate the player</string>
      <string name="music_chose">Please choose the default player</string>
      <string name="music_open">Open</string>
      <string name="music_set_title">Set the default music app</string>
      <string name="music_set_bt_note">Player Settings success</string>
      <string name="music_set_click">Player Settings successfully exit the current players after a long press to open a new player.</string>
      <string name="music_set_play">Player setup is successful, the Bluetooth restart to take effect after exiting the current player.</string>
      <string name="protocol">Disclaimer Agreement</string>
      <string name="protocol_check_cont">I have read and agree to the"Bluetooth FM exemption agreement"</string>
      <string name="protocol_ok">Confirm</string>
      <string name="protocol_mi_protocol">User Agreement</string>
      <string name="protocol_mi_privacy_policyl">Privacy Policy</string>
      <string name="protocol_load_fail">User Agreement loading failed!</string>
      <string name="protocol_title_1">1. General Provisions</string>
      <string name="protocol_content_1">
    "
    1, the user agrees to the terms of this Agreement and follow the instructions on the page to complete all registration procedures. The user during the registration process, click on the"Agree"button it means that the user and the meter Wuxi Rui Information Technology Co., Ltd. reached an agreement, accepted all the terms of this Agreement.

    2, the user registration is successful, Wuxi Rui Information Technology Co., Ltd. meters will give each user a user account and corresponding password, the user ID and password from the user responsible for the custody; users should all activities and events in their user account's legal liability.

    3, the user can use Bluetooth FM channels each individual service, when a user uses Bluetooth FM each individual service, the user's behavior as the terms of their service to the individual services as well as Bluetooth FM issued at the individual service agreed class bulletin.

    4, Bluetooth FM Member Service Agreement and various announcements by the Terms of Service and Information Technology Co., Ltd. Wuxi Rui meters updated and revised without notice. When you use related services, Bluetooth FM should be concerned about this updated and revised notice, and comply with the terms they use.

    Before you use Bluetooth FM to provide the services, the service should read this Agreement carefully. If you do not agree with and /or modification of the Service at any time, you can take the initiative to cancel the service provided by Bluetooth FM; once you use Bluetooth FM service is deemed to have understood and fully agree with the content of the Service Agreement , including any modifications meters Wuxi Rui Information Technology Co., Ltd. made at any time of the service agreement, and become Bluetooth FM users."
  </string>
      <string name="protocol_title_2">2. Privacy</string>
      <string name="protocol_content_2">
    "
    1, Bluetooth FM account (ie Bluetooth FM user ID) of rice owned by Wuxi Rui Information Technology Co., Ltd., the user complete the registration formalities, Bluetooth FM obtained the right to use the account. Users should provide timely, accurate and detailed personal information and update registration information, with timely, detailed and accurate requirements, all the original type of information will be used for registration information. If the problem is due to the registration information is untrue and caused problems and consequences occur, rice Wuxi Rui Information Technology Co. assumes no responsibility.

    2, users should not be account, password, transfer, sell or lends to others, if the meter Wuxi Rui Information Technology Co., found the user account is not registered himself, Wuxi Rui meter IT Ltd reserves the right to discontinue service. If users find that their account has been illegally used by others, you should immediately notify meters Wuxi Rui Information Technology Co. A result of hacking or user violation of this agreement lead to account, password illegal use by others, and assumes all legal liability and loss caused by the user himself, Wuxi Rui Information Technology Co., rice does not bear any responsibility.

    3, Wuxi Rui Information Technology Co., rice is not open to the public or to provide a single user registration information to third parties unless:
    (1) prior express authorization of the user;
    (2) only disclose your personal information to provide you requested products and services;
    (3) in accordance with relevant legal and regulatory requirements;
    (4) in accordance with the requirements of the relevant government departments;
    (5) To safeguard the legitimate rights and interests of Wuxi Rui Information Technology Co., Ltd. meters.

    4, registered users Bluetooth FM account, use other Bluetooth FM products or services, visit Bluetooth FM website, or participate in promotions and prize games, Bluetooth FM collect user's personally identifiable information. Information Technology Co., Ltd. Wuxi Rui meter will not provide to any third party, sell, lease, share trading and the user's personally identifiable information. However, the user agrees meters Wuxi Rui Information Technology Co., a user's personally identifiable information to improve services and web content provided.

    5, when the user uses Bluetooth FM products and services, a variety of data and information Bluetooth FM will be actively or passively collect and access the user's behavior arising; including but not limited to location information, IP address, device information , cookies, etc; user hereby irrevocably consent Wuxi Rui information Technology Co., Ltd. meters above the right to use the data and information, and in order to enhance Bluetooth FM products, improved Bluetooth FM service purposes, the data and information provided to the third parties.

    6, when the user uses Bluetooth FM products and services, in order to provide better service, Bluetooth FM possible through your phone using a variety of positioning technology, the user hereby irrevocably consent to use this technology Bluetooth FM for customer service, and we agreed Bluetooth FM authorize third parties to use these technologies to provide users with services."
  </string>
      <string name="protocol_title_3">3. Terms of Service</string>
      <string name="protocol_content_3">
    "
    1, the user when using Bluetooth FM service, you must comply with the provisions of relevant laws and regulations of the People's Republic of China, the user should agree to not use the Service for any illegal or improper activity, including, but not limited to the following acts:
    · Uploaded, displayed, posted, transmitted or otherwise transmit the letter containing the following contents;
    · The basic principles of the Constitution against the determined;
    · Endangering national security, leaking state secrets, subverting state power, undermining national unity;
    · Harm national honor and interests;
    · Incitement to ethnic hatred, ethnic discrimination, undermining national unity;
    · Violate the state religion policies or propagate cult and feudal superstition;
    · Walking rumors, disturbs social order or undermines social stability;
    · Walking obscenity, pornography, gambling, violence, homicide, terror or instigate crimes;
    · Insult or slander others, infringe upon the legitimate rights of others;
    · Contain false, harmful, threatening, infringes on privacy, harassing, tortuous, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, or other morally sense of content;
    · Containing Chinese laws, regulations, rules, regulations and how to regulate the legal validity of having a restricted or prohibited by other content;
    • Do not for any unlawful purpose and the use of network services system;
    · Do not use Bluetooth FM services in the following activities;
    * Without permission, access to computer information network or use the computer information network resources;
    * Without permission of the computer information network functions to delete, modify or increase;
    * Without permission, to enter the computer information network, storage, processing or transmission of data and applications to delete, modify or increase;
    · Intentionally spreading computer viruses and other destructive programs;
    · Other acts that endanger the safety of computer information network;

    Any claim, loss or claim 2, user violation of the provisions of this Agreement or the Terms of Service, arising or resulting from any third party claims, including reasonable attorneys' fees, you agree to indemnify Wuxi Rui Information Technology Co., rice and cooperation, affiliates, make it from damage. In this regard, Wuxi Rui Information Technology Co., Ltd. is entitled meters depending on the nature of the user's behavior, including but not limited to taking delete users to publish content, suspended license, termination of service, restrictions on the use, recycling Bluetooth FM account, legal liability and other measures . Car Bluetooth FM malicious registered account or use Bluetooth FM account for illegal activities, trouble, harassment, fraud, and other violations of other users of this Agreement, Wuxi Rui Information Technology Co., Ltd. is entitled meters recover their account. At the same time, Wuxi Rui Information Technology Co., Ltd. will, as the rice requirements of justice, assist in the investigation.

    3, the user may not use the Service or any part of the Service or obtain, copy, copy, sell, resell or exploit for any other commercial purposes.

    4, the user must use their own Bluetooth FM service process acts liable. User liability forms include, but are not limited to: compensation for those who have been violated, as well as in Wuxi Rui Information Technology Co., Ltd. meters first assumed the administrative penalties or liability for damages resulting from infringement by user behavior, the user should be given Wuxi Rui meters Information Technology Co., equal compensation."
  </string>
      <string name="protocol_title_4">4. Services</string>
      <string name="protocol_content_4">
    "
    1, the specific content of Bluetooth FM network services provided by the Information Technology Co., Ltd. Wuxi Rui meter according to the actual situation.

    2, unless the service agreement as otherwise expressly provided in other, Information Technology Co., Ltd. Wuxi Rui meter launch of new products, new features, new services, shall be subject to the Service Agreement.

    3, in order to use this service, you must be responsible for obtaining legal qualifications to provide you with third-party Internet access services, access to international Internet and related services should pay for their own expenses. In addition, you must be responsible for themselves and equipped with all necessary international networking to connect the equipment needed, including a computer, modem or other access device;

    4, given the special nature of network services, users agree Wuxi Rui meter IT Ltd reserves the right without prior notice, to change, suspend or terminate some or all network services. Wuxi Rui Information Technology Co., rice does not guarantee network services will not be interrupted, the timeliness of network services, security, accuracy is not guaranteed.

    5, Wuxi Rui Information Technology Co., Ltd. meters require regular or irregular basis to provide network services platform or related equipment repair or maintenance, as a result of such circumstances and cause of network services (including service charges) within a reasonable time of the interruption, Wuxi Rui Information Technology Co., rice will not bear any responsibility. Information Technology Co., Ltd. Wuxi Rui meters reservations without prior notice for the maintenance, upgrade or other purposes suspend any portion of the Service.

    6, the Service or third parties may provide, links to your site on the Internet or other resources. Since the meter Wuxi Rui Information Technology Co. has no control over such sites and resources, you acknowledge and agree that such sites or resources available, Wuxi Rui Information Technology Co., Ltd. is not responsible for rice, the presence or derived from such sites or resources for any content, advertising, products or other materials, rice Wuxi Rui information Technology Co., also does not guarantee or be responsible. Use of or reliance on any such sites or resources posted or through any damage or loss of any content, goods or services such sites or resources acquired generated by the meter Wuxi Rui Information Technology Co. does not assume any responsibility.

    7, the user expressly agrees that the use of risk Bluetooth FM network services will be entirely their own risk. Users understand and accept the download, or any information obtained through Bluetooth FM service depends on the users themselves by their commitment system damage, data loss, and any other risks. Information Technology Co., Ltd. Wuxi Rui meters of any goods online shopping service in the service obtained, the transaction process, job postings, are not guaranteed.

    8,6 months without landing account, Wuxi Rui Information Technology Co., Ltd. meters off rights reserved.

    9, Wuxi Rui meter IT Ltd reserves the right at any time to modify or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, Bluetooth FM service (or any part thereof), regardless of whether or not notice, Information Technology Co., Ltd. Wuxi Rui meter users and any third All three need not bear any responsibility.

    10, termination of service
    You agree Bluetooth FM in its sole discretion based on consideration, for any reason, including but not limited to, prolonged use, or Bluetooth FM believe that you have violated the text and the spirit of the service agreement, terminate your password, account number or the Service the use, and take you to remove any content within the service and delete. You agree that any provision of services under this Agreement to provide this service, can be interrupted or terminated without prior notice, you acknowledge and agree that Bluetooth FM can deactivate or delete your account and your account all relevant information and documents immediately. In addition, you agree to use the Service is interrupted or terminated or your account number and related information and files are closed or deleted, Bluetooth FM to you or any third party shall not bear any responsibility."
  </string>
      <string name="protocol_title_5">5. Other</string>
      <string name="protocol_content_5">
    "
    1, to enter into this agreement, implementation and interpretation and dispute settlement should apply the law People's Republic of China.

    2. The two sides on the implementation of the contents of this Agreement or any dispute, both sides should be settled through friendly consultations; negotiation fails, either party may bring a lawsuit to Wuxi Rui Information Technology Co., Ltd. meter location People's Court.

    3, Bluetooth FM does not exercise or enforce any right or provision of the service agreement does not constitute a waiver of such right or.

    4. any provision of this Agreement for whatever reason, completely or partially invalid or unenforceable, the remaining provisions of this Agreement remain valid and binding.

    You found any violation of the service agreement and any other terms of service of the individual services, please notify the Information Technology Co., Ltd. Wuxi Rui meters.

    This product is in driving the process to bring you a lot of convenience, but for your driving safety, we strongly recommend that you driving the process according to the rules proper use of this product, all kinds of traffic accidents in the process due to improper use, Wuxi Rui m Information Technology Co., Ltd. will not be responsible."
  </string>
      <string name="shake_song">Song shake</string>
      <string name="shake_song_tip">Warning: Some phones does\'t support the song shake feature</string>.
      <string name="phone_voice_title">Ringtones projection</string>
      <string name="push_activity">Push activity</string>
      <string name="setting">Settings</string>
      <string name="update">Check for updates</string>
      <string name="update_title">Software update</string>
      <string name="update_info">Detect whether a new version</string>
      <string name="update_state_no">You\'re using the latest version</string>
      <string name="update_state_yes">A new version is available</string>
      <string name="update_timeout">Request timed out!</string>
      <string name="update_not_find_file">Apk file not found!</string>
      <string name="update_getInfo">Checking is there a new version...</string>
      <string name="update_download_info">Downloading a new version...%1$s</string>
      <string name="update_download_progress">%1$s/%2$s</string>
      <string name="update_download_fail">Download failed! Please try again later.</string>
      <string name="update_download_again">Download again</string>
      <string name="update_latest">This is the latest version</string>
      <string name="update_latest_version">The new version is detected: %1$s</string>
      <string name="update_download">Update</string>
      <string name="update_install">Install</string>
      <string name="update_dialog_title">New version available, update it! (Version V%1$s)</string>
      <string name="update_dialog_title_force">New version available, to continue using this app you have to update this app!</string>
      <string name="update_dialog_not_update">Update later</string>
      <string name="update_dialog_update">Update now</string>
      <string name="voice_title">Voice prompts</string>
      <string name="voice_mode_close">disable</string>
      <string name="voice_info">whether music app every time you start a voice reminder</string>
      <string name="voice_info_title">is turned on voice prompts (fatigue driving, turn on the player, etc.)?</string>
      <string name="key_pair_none">Dongle unpaired</string>
      <string name="key_pairing">Dongle pairing</string>
      <string name="key_not_pair">Dongle not paired</string>
      <string name="key_pair_success">Dongle paired successfully</string>
      <string name="key_pair_fail">Pairing failed</string>
      <string name="key_pair_tip1">please click operation pairing</string>
      <string name="key_pair_tip2">press both the upper and lower key pair</string>
      <string name="key_pair_tip3">Welcome back</string>
      <string name="key_pair_tip4">Click below to re-pair</string>
      <string name="key_pair_change_direction">switch left and right keys to control the direction</string>
      <string name="key_pair_buy">Purchase button</string>
      <string name="key_pair_begin">Start pairing</string>
      <string name="key_pair_title">Pair</string>
      <string name="key_pair_rebegin">Re-pair</string>
</resources>
